<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>John Graham | Portfolio</title><description>A portfolio and blog showcasing web development projects and technical articles.</description><link>https://crohnos.github.io/portfolio-blog/</link><item><title>Building AI-Author: My Journey Creating an Interactive Story Generator</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/building-ai-author-interactive-story-generator/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/building-ai-author-interactive-story-generator/</guid><description>When I set out to build AI-Author, I had a clear vision - create a platform where users could generate personalized stories with the help of AI.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Building a Specialized Inventory Management System for Non-Profits</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/building-cac-inventory-management-system/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/building-cac-inventory-management-system/</guid><description>When I first met with the Community Aid Center (CAC), they described a common challenge faced by many non-profits - tracking donated inventory effectively with limited resources.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creating an Internal Merchandise Store: Simplifying Company Swag Distribution</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/creating-an-internal-merch-store/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/creating-an-internal-merch-store/</guid><description>Company merchandise is more than just branded swag—it&apos;s a tangible expression of company culture and team unity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Developing a Job Application Tracker for The Joshua Center</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/developing-the-joshua-center-job-app-tracker/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/developing-the-joshua-center-job-app-tracker/</guid><description>When The Joshua Center approached me about building a job application tracking system, I saw an opportunity to create something that would genuinely help both the organization and the people they serve.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DoorDash Addiction</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/doordash-addiction-epidemic/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/doordash-addiction-epidemic/</guid><description>I&apos;ll admit it upfront - I&apos;ve been a DoorDash addict. For nearly three years, I ordered food delivery 4-5 times weekly, watching my savings dwindle while my waistline expanded. What started as an occasional convenience during busy workweeks gradually morphed into a default behavior.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tool Overanalyzer</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/comparison-go-rust-web-game-dev/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/comparison-go-rust-web-game-dev/</guid><description>When deciding on a programming language for your next project, Go and Rust frequently emerge as modern contenders with enthusiastic communities. Having worked with both in professional settings for web and game development, I&apos;d like to share an honest, experience-based comparison of these languages across these different domains.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Web Dev Tools I Use</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/the-tools-i-use-for-web-dev/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/the-tools-i-use-for-web-dev/</guid><description>As a web developer, your choice of tools can dramatically impact your productivity, code quality, and overall enjoyment of the development process. Over the years, I&apos;ve experimented with countless frameworks, libraries, and tools before settling on my current tech stack.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>