<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>John Graham | Full-Stack Developer</title><description>Full-Stack Developer specialized in React, TypeScript, Node.js, and modern web applications. Portfolio showcasing projects and technical articles.</description><link>https://crohnos.github.io/portfolio-blog/</link><item><title>Rainbow Room Inventory: Crafting Management Tools for Children&apos;s Advocacy Center</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/building-cac-inventory-management-system/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/building-cac-inventory-management-system/</guid><description>I developed a full-stack inventory tracking web application for the Children&apos;s Advocacy Center&apos;s &quot;Rainbow Room&quot; to track donated items, manage categories and sizes, generate QR codes, handle photos, and import/export data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creating an Internal Merchandise Store: Simplifying Company Swag Distribution</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/creating-an-internal-merch-store/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/creating-an-internal-merch-store/</guid><description>Company merchandise is more than just branded swag—it&apos;s a tangible expression of company culture and team unity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Developing a Job Application Tracker for The Joshua Center</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/developing-the-joshua-center-job-app-tracker/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/projects/developing-the-joshua-center-job-app-tracker/</guid><description>When The Joshua Center approached me about building a job application tracking system, I saw an opportunity to create something that would genuinely help both the organization and the people they serve.</description><pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Escape from the Audit Labyrinth: Why I Left IT Audit Behind</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/personal/why-i-quit-it-audit/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/personal/why-i-quit-it-audit/</guid><description>Three years ago, I was sitting in a beige conference room reviewing yet another spreadsheet of control matrices when I had a realization - I was deeply, profoundly unfulfilled.</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Pay-to-Win Paradox: The Ethical Problem with Microtransactions</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/articles/the-immorality-of-microtransactions/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/articles/the-immorality-of-microtransactions/</guid><description>As someone who has been gaming since the NES era, I&apos;ve witnessed the industry&apos;s evolution from simple cartridge games to today&apos;s complex digital ecosystems with troubling microtransactions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The DoorDash Dilemma: My Delivery App Addiction</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/doordash-addiction-epidemic/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/doordash-addiction-epidemic/</guid><description>I&apos;ll admit it upfront - I&apos;ve been a DoorDash addict. For nearly three years, I ordered food delivery 4-5 times weekly, watching my savings dwindle while my waistline expanded. What started as an occasional convenience during busy workweeks gradually morphed into a default behavior.</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Convergence of Creativity: Game Development as Artistic Fusion</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/articles/game-dev-as-creative-intersection/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/articles/game-dev-as-creative-intersection/</guid><description>Game development occupies a unique space in the creative landscape – it&apos;s perhaps the only medium that demands mastery across multiple creative disciplines.</description><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Notes of Knowledge: How Being a Band Nerd Shaped My Learning Process</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/personal/being-a-band-nerd-taught-me-to-learn/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/personal/being-a-band-nerd-taught-me-to-learn/</guid><description>Growing up as a self-proclaimed &quot;band nerd,&quot; I spent countless hours in practice rooms, rehearsals, and performances. What I didn&apos;t realize then was that those experiences were teaching me not just about music, but about the fundamental process of learning itself.</description><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Language Showdown: Go vs Rust for Web and Game Development</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/comparison-go-rust-web-game-dev/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/comparison-go-rust-web-game-dev/</guid><description>When deciding on a programming language for your next project, Go and Rust frequently emerge as modern contenders with enthusiastic communities. Having worked with both in professional settings for web and game development, I&apos;d like to share an honest, experience-based comparison of these languages across these different domains.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Web Dev Tools I Use</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/the-tools-i-use-for-web-dev/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/the-tools-i-use-for-web-dev/</guid><description>As a web developer, your choice of tools can dramatically impact your productivity, code quality, and overall enjoyment of the development process. Over the years, I&apos;ve experimented with countless frameworks, libraries, and tools before settling on my current tech stack.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JavaScript Journey: The Ultimate Learning Resource Guide</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/tutorials/the-best-resources-for-learning-javascript/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/tutorials/the-best-resources-for-learning-javascript/</guid><description>JavaScript has become one of the most essential languages for web development, powering everything from interactive websites to complex web applications. Here&apos;s my compilation of favorite resources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Markdown Mastery: Beyond the Basics</title><link>https://crohnos.github.io/posts/tutorials/learning-react/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://crohnos.github.io/posts/tutorials/learning-react/</guid><description>After mastering the basics of Markdown, it&apos;s time to dive into some advanced techniques that will make your documentation, READMEs, and technical writing stand out.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>